＜５年以下の懲役 または➡
50万円以下の
罰金に処せられます＞
＜後悔しても 元には戻せない＞
不正視聴!?
(ウタカタ)そこは オレの指定席だ。
That seat is reserved for me...
(ホタル)ウタカタ様！
Sir Utakata!
(ウタカタ)遁兵衛が呼んでるぞ。
Tonbei is looking for you.
(遁兵衛)頼んだぞ。
I'm counting on you.
(アカボシ)またか！
Not again.
(チュウシン)こんな だだっ広い平原に
いくつも罠を仕掛けるたぁな…。
They sure went through
a lot of trouble
setting up this many traps on
such an open field.
ご苦労なこった。
何者かが罠を突破し
砦に迫っております。
Someone is breaking through our traps
and approaching our fort.
念のため 先代の教えに従い
木ノ葉隠れの里に➡
Just in case, in accordance with
the late master's instructions,
I have alerted the Hidden Leaf.
緊急の知らせを放ちました。
並大抵の者では この砦に
近づくこともできませぬが➡
It's impossible for any ordinary person
to get close to our fort.
もし ここまで
敵が押し寄せてきたときは…。
However, if the enemy does succeed
in getting here...
ウタカタ様と３人
力を合わせて戦えば大丈夫。
The three of us, including Sir Utakata,
just have to fight together!
We'll turn the tables on them!
返り討ちです！
なぜ ここが狙われる？
ヤツらの目的は いったい何だ？
Why are they targeting us?
What is their purpose?
おそらく… 我ら一族に伝わる
禁術かと…。
Most likely...
the Forbidden Jutsu that has been
passed down to our clan.
(チュウシン)トラップをかわし続けて
砦に近づけば深い谷。
All these traps,
then as you near the fort,
there's a deep ravine...
更に その向こうに
結界まで張っちゃって。
On top of which is
a barrier beyond that.
ヘッ どんだけ心配性なヤツらなんだ。
Talk about being overly cautious.
なあ そう思わねえか？ ナンゴウ。
Don't you think so, Nango?
(ナンゴウ)あぁ。
Yeah...
(チュウシン)相変わらず
会話がふくらまないね お前は…。
You're just not a man of many words...
are you?
(ベンテン)ムダ話は
そのへんにしときな。 チュウシン。
Chushin, enough of your rambling.
口が軽いと
オツムの中も軽く見えるぞ。
A loose mouth is indicative of
an empty brain.
口を開けば イメージ悪くなるのは
お前のほうじゃないのかい ベンテン。
I'd say you're the one who looks bad
each time you open your mouth.
Benten...
(アカボシ)相手が
必死に守ろうとするのは➡
Going through the extremes to
protect something is proof of its value!
それだけ価値がある
という証拠だ！
陣形を取れ！
Get into your positions.
《アカボシ : あそこか…》
That must be it...
破!!
なに！ 結界が破られた。
What?! The barrier has been broken.
ヤツら… ただ者ではないな。
These guys...are not ordinary people.
ベンテン！
任せろ！
Benten!
Leave them to me!
お次は山登りか。
Next is mountain climbing.
(遁兵衛)ホタル様 これを…。
Lady Hotaru, take this...
おじい様から伝わりし
禁術を守るため➡
In order to protect the Forbidden Jutsu
that your grandfather passed down,
ひとまず 一族の隠れる山里へ
ウタカタ様とともに お逃げくだされ。
you and Sir Utakata must escape
to our hidden village.
遁兵衛は…。
すぐに あとを追いまする。
What about you?
I will follow immediately.
Now you must hurry...
さあ 早く…。
ダメです！
No! If we're to escape,
the three of us will go together.
逃げるなら３人一緒に。
The enemy is at our doorstep.
敵は すぐそばまで
迫っているのですぞ。
今は そのようなワガママを
言っている場合では。
This is not the time for
self-indulgence.
来ないのか？
You're not coming?
さぁ ホタル様。
Go, Lady Hotaru.
ウタカタ殿。
Sir Utakata!
Please...take care of Lady Hotaru.
ホタル様のこと
くれぐれも お頼み申す。
The debt I owe you will be repaid...
借りは返す。
わ～ おっとっと…。
Phew, that was close.
いや 危な…。
ただの山登りじゃ
すまないらしいぜ アカボシ。
This isn't gonna be
an ordinary climb, Akaboshi.
頂上じゃ
何が待ち受けているのか➡
I can't wait to see what's waiting
for us at the summit.
楽しみになってきたな。
(遁兵衛)ホタル様
道中くれぐれも油断なきよう。
Lady Hotaru...
Please be extremely careful
while traveling.
ウタカタ様のおそばを
決して離れては いけませんぞ。
You must not leave Sir Utakata's side.
遁兵衛 必ず後から来るのですよ。
Tonbei, you must follow us later.
Promise me that!
約束です。
ホタル様は➡
Lady Hotaru, think only of
your own safety. Nothing else!
自身の安全のみを心配なされ！
《役の行者様
一時でも時間を稼ぎ…》
Lord En no Gyoja... I promise to buy
as much time as possible...
《ホタル様を お守りする》
So I can protect Lady Hotaru!
(シズネ)綱手様 このようなものが。
Lady Tsunade, we received this...
(綱手)なに!?
What?!
(カツユ)あぁ～！
(カカシ)カツユ様。
あぁ カカシさん。
Lady Katsuyu!
Oh, Kakashi...
(キバ)なんだ カツユ様が
わざわざ お出迎えか？
What? Lady Katsuyu came
all the way to greet us?
No, she didn't.
(シノ)いや 違う。
どうやら
厄介ごとが起こったらしい。
There must be trouble.
Because...
なぜなら…。
(ヤマト)綱手様がカツユ様を
お使いになるのは➡
Lady Tsunade only uses
Lady Katsuyu during emergencies.
緊急のときだけだろうから。
I get it! So there's an urgent situation.
なるほど 緊急事態ってことか。
I know how you feel, Shino...
《ヒナタ : シノ君 わかるわ。
When you aren't allowed to finish
what you wanted to say...
言いたいことが
言えなかったときの気持…》
A secret treaty?
(シズネ)密約… ですか？
During the Third Great Ninja War,
a certain jutsu passed down
第三次忍界大戦のとき➡
土蜘蛛一族の頭領
役の行者が伝えるある術が➡
by En no Gyoja, the leader
of the Tsuchigumo Clan,
wiped out an entire village.
里一つを丸ごと焼き尽くした。
(綱手)あまりに危険なその術を➡
The Third Hokage demanded that
such a dangerous jutsu
禁術にするよう要請したのが➡
be classified as a Forbidden Jutsu.
三代目火影 その代償として➡
And in exchange, it was agreed that
the Hidden Leaf would provide aid
土蜘蛛一族が
危機に陥ったときには➡
to the Tsuchigumo clan
in time of danger.
木ノ葉が守るという
約束を交わした。
(カツユ)カカシさんは 報告のため
里に戻るようにとのことです。
Kakashi, you are to report to the village
for details from your last mission.
わかりました。
Understood.
事は一刻を争う。
We're battling against time.
Team 7 will go with Captain Yamato
第七班は隊長のヤマトと共に➡
and head for
Mount Katsuragi immediately.
大至急 葛城山へ向かえ。
(サクラ)はい。
Yes, sir!
(ナルト)なぁ なんでカカシ先生が
一緒じゃねんだ？
Why aren't you coming,
Kakashi Sensei?
(サクラ)えっ!?
ボクでは不満だと？
Is there a problem if it's just me?
That's not what I meant...
そういう意味じゃ
ねえってばよ。
すでに 役の行者は
１年前に亡くなり➡
En no Gyoja passed away a year ago
and the fort on Mount Katsuragi
葛城山の砦には➡
is occupied by his granddaughter,
Hotaru, and her servant.
孫娘のホタルが 従者１人と
ともに暮らしている。
砦を襲うヤツらの目的は➡
Whoever is attacking the fort
is undoubtedly
役の行者の
禁術に違いない。
after En no Gyoja's Forbidden Jutsu.
禁術が
他の忍に奪われることは➡
We must prevent the theft of
the Forbidden Jutsu at all cost.
なんとしても
防がねばならない。
ナルト君を向かわせたのは…。
Why did you send Naruto too?
It's a countermeasure against
the Akatsuki.
(綱手)対 暁の対策として
泳がせる意味もある。
電！
光！
石！
火！
(チュウシン)このジジイ １人で砦を
守りきるつもりだったのかねぇ。
Did this old man intend to
protect the fort all by himself?
(アカボシ)しかし 思ったより
手間取った。
Still, this took longer than planned.
急いで捜索開始だ。
Let's hurry and start the search.
That's the Tsuchigumo clan's fort?!
あれが 土蜘蛛一族の砦…。
Captain Yamato!
ヤマト隊長。
Hm?
ここで 何があったんだ？
What happened here?
It doesn't look like this is from a fight...
戦闘ではなさそうだ。
サイ どうだい？
Sai, how about it?
(サイ)砦の方向に
向かっている新しい足跡が。
There are fresh footprints headed
towards the fort...
敵は４人です。
The enemy is a group of four.
These are from traps surrounding
the fort.
これは
砦の周りのトラップだよ。
敵は うまく
かわしたらしいけどね。
It looks like the enemy avoided them.
じゃあ このあたりには
まだ罠が？
Then there are more in this area?
だから このトラップの跡を
たどっていけばいいってことさ。
We'll just follow the trail of trap marks.
そっか それなら
罠にひっかからずに➡
I get it!
That way, we'll get to the fort
without encountering any fresh traps!
砦まで行けるってわけか。
役の行者の禁術は
どこに隠した!!
Where is the Forbidden Jutsu
of En no Gyoja?!
You lost, so 'fess up.
お前は負けたんだ 潔く吐け。
(遁兵衛)知らん。
I know nothing.
(チュウシン)しらばっくれても
ムダだってんだよ！
Playing dumb is useless!
孫娘…。
ん？
The granddaughter.
That's right. En no Gyoja
has a granddaughter.
そういやあ ここには
役の行者の孫娘がいるはずだな。
Did you let her escape?
娘を逃がしたか。
禁術もソイツが？
She has the Forbidden Jutsu?
そうなんだな おい!!
Is that it? Hey!
もういい。
それなら 見当はついてる。
Enough. I know where to find her.
そろそろ 潮時だ。
We're out of time.
It seems we have some interference.
どうやら ジャマ者が現れたようだ。
ヤマト隊長
行き止まりだってばよ。
It's a dead-end, Captain Yamato.
(ヤマト)なら 橋を架ければ
いいだけさ。
We'll just lay a bridge across it.
木遁の術！
Wood Style!
さっすが ヤマト隊長！
Gotta hand it to you, Captain Yamato!
ボクが一緒で
よかったでしょ？
Aren't you glad I was here?
Don't rub it in.
しつこいってばよ！
しっかりしろ じいさん。
Hang on, old man!
弱いけど脈はあるわ。
助かる。
It's weak, but he still has a pulse.
He'll live.
We were one step too late...
ひと足遅かったか。
サイ 他に誰かいないか
周辺を調べてくれ。
Sai, check the area to see
if there are any others.
はい。
Right.
You've come to...
気がついたか？
私たちは 木ノ葉隠れの里より
警護のために派遣された者です。
We are from the Hidden Leaf
and were dispatched to
provide assistance.
あなたは
ホタル様の従者とお見うけするが。
You are Lady Hotaru's servant,
I presume?
私は 遁兵衛です。
I am...Tonbei...
ホ… ホタル様は➡
L-Lady Hotaru is headed for
土蜘蛛一族が隠れ住む
山里に向かいました。
the hidden village of
the Tsuchigumo clan.
屋敷の奥に 入口を崩された
抜け穴らしきものがある。
There is an escape route with
a collapsed entry
in the back of the mansion.
そこを通って ホタル様は…。
Lady Hotaru went...through there...
わかりました。
我々も あとを追います。
I understand. We will follow her.
サクラ！ このまま 遁兵衛殿の治療を
続けてくれ。
Sakura, stay here and tend
to Sir Tonbei's injuries.
はい！
ナルト！ サイ！ すぐに出発だ！
Right.
Naruto, Sai, let's go.
(ホタル)ウタカタ様。
Sir Utakata, there's something
I'd like to ask you...
お聞きしたいことが
あるのですが…。
隠れ里に着いたあとも➡
Will you teach me jutsu even
after we get to the hidden village?
私に 術を教えてくださいますか？
オレは 何も教えたつもりはない。
I don't recall teaching you anything.
でも 砦では➡
But back at the fort,
you trained me in many things.
いろいろな修業を
つけてくださって…！
それは お前が
勝手にやっていたことだ。
You did that on your own...
それに…
里に着けば オレは用なしだ。
Also, when we reach the village,
I will no longer be needed.
ウタカタ様ほど強いお人は
里にはいません！
There's no one stronger than you
in the village!
それに私は ウタカタ様に
お教えいただきたいのです！
And I want you to teach me.
That time, when you saved me...
あの時
私を助けていただいたとき…！
((キャ～ッ!!
しつこいヤツらだ！
Persistent guys...
《なに？ あの術！ すごい！》
What is...that jutsu?
It's amazing!
これで ヤツらに
居場所を知られたな！
Now they know my location...
しばらく 人目を避けて
移動しなければ…。
For the time being,
I must stay out of view as I move.
Are you all right?!
大丈夫ですか!?
その傷…。
That wound...
よろしければ 私たちの砦で➡
Allow me to treat it back at our fort.
治療させてもらえませんか？
助けていただいたお礼といっては
なんですが…。
That's the least I can do
for coming to my aid.
《砦？》
Fort?
うっ！
あっ！
しっかりしてください！
Please hang on!
今 助けを呼んできます！
I'm going to get help.
Don't move from this spot!
(それまで
ここで ジッとしていてください！))
- Damn! I used too much chakra.
- I'll be right back...
《ウタカタ : クソッ！
チャクラを使いすぎだ…な…》
あの時 私も➡
At that time, I wanted to become
like you, Sir Utakata!
ウタカタ様のように
なりたいと思ったのです！
オレは別に
お前を助けたわけじゃない。
I didn't save you that time...
でも…！
But...!
The ninja who attacked were coming
after me, not you.
襲ってきた忍たちは お前じゃなく
オレを狙っていたのだ。
オレは 自分の身を守るために
戦っただけだ。
I just fought in order to protect myself.
そうだとしても➡
Even so, after watching you,
私は ウタカタ様を見て
強くなりたいと思ったんです！
I knew I wanted to be strong
like you. No, I must.
いえ… 強くならなければ
いけないんです！
そのために ウタカタ様の術を…！
That is why I wish to learn your jutsu...
強ければいいのか？
えっ？
Being strong is enough for you?
Huh?
人に つけ狙われるような人間に
教えてもらったことを➡
You may end up regretting being taught
by one who is a wanted man.
あとで 後悔するように
なるかもしれないぞ。
私は ウタカタ様を信じています。
I trust you, Sir Utakata.
どんなことがあっても
ウタカタ様を 一生 師匠として…。
No matter what happens,
I will always consider you my master.
オレを師匠と呼ぶな!!
Don't call me your master!
しまった！
その子から離れろ！
Shoot!
Step away from that girl!
A Shadow Clone?
《影分身？
面倒な…》
What a bother...
おとなしく 捕まりやが…。
Give it up and be captured--!
No!
ダメ！
その方は 敵ではありません！
He is not an enemy!
(ヤマト)ナルト！
Naruto!
早とちりしたようで
すみませんでした。
Pardon him for jumping to conclusions.
遁兵衛殿より ホタル様のことだけは
聞いていたのですが。
Sir Tonbei had told us only
about Lady Hotaru...
遁兵衛は 無事なんですね？
はい。
Tonbei is alive and well?
Yes. He's under the care
of our medic.
今 医療班が看護しています。
よかった。
I'm glad...
(ヤマト)ここからは 我々も
護衛に加わります。
From here on, you have
our protection as well.
ほんとに 悪かったってばよ。
Hey, I'm really sorry.
あとは任せても 大丈夫だな？
I can leave the rest to you then...
Huh?
ああ。
任務は きっちり やりぬくって…。
Sure thing!
I always fulfill my missions...
Huh?
世話になった。 じゃあな。
Thanks... Take care.
ウタカタ様！
Sir Utakata!
おい！ どこ行くんだ？
Hey, where're you going?
せめて 隠れ里まで
一緒に行ってもらえませんか？
Can't you at least stay with me until
we reach the hidden village?
アイツらは 強い。
頼っても大丈夫だ。
Those guys are strong...
You can rely on them.
私には 護衛よりも 術を
教えてくれる人が必要なのです。
I don't need guards!
I need someone to teach me jutsu!
お願いです。 私と一緒に…。
Come with me, please...
修業は
今まで以上に真剣にやります！
I'll be more serious than ever
in my training!
どんなにつらい訓練でも
決して泣きごとは言いません！
I'll endure anything and
I promise never to cry! And...
そして ウタカタ様を
二度と師匠とは…。
And I'll never call you
my master...ever...again...
師匠とは…。
Stupid Master Utakata!
ウタカタ師匠のバカ～!!
それは 禁句だと言っただろ。
I told you not to call me that...
オレは 師匠と呼ばれるほど
バカじゃない。
I'm not foolish enough to
be called master.
Why are you people following me?
同期のなか ただ１人
いまだ下忍のままの➡
うずまきナルト君。
今日のお客様です！
なんか
テンション下がる紹介だなぁ。
台本に そう書いてあるもんでね。
今日は 台本
忘れなかったんだな。
ああっ！ まだ そのことを言う！
だって２回もだぜ！
この間は カカシ先輩が
持ってただけだろ！
じゃあ １回目は？
あの日の台本は
トイレに行っている間に➡
なくなっていて そのあと➡
ラーメンの汁まみれで
発見されたんだ。
ん？ ラーメンの汁？
((ヘヘヘ… 休憩中に ラーメン ラーメンと。
だっ あっ！ げ～っ！
やっべえ！
誰の台本だってばよ？
あ～ どうしよう？ どうしよう？
こうなりゃ 証拠隠滅！
ふぅ～ これでよし。
(本番で～す！
ああ 今 行くってばよ！))
あれが ヤマト隊長… の!?
やっぱり… お前か！
出た～っ!!
＜ルーシィ : それは 天にも地にも→
いまだかつて現れたことなき
怪異の顕現＞
＜ その異様な姿が
人々の前に立ち現れしとき→
誰もが異様な冷気を
肌身に感じたのであった＞
もう逃げられんぞ 連続宝石強盗！